[
  {
  "appointmentId": "132265465",
  "appointmentInfo": {
    "fullAddress": "18715 Keystone Oak Street, Houston",
    "listingId": 41156570,
    "listingAgent": "Jordan Delaney Miller",
    "office": "Keller Williams Woodlands",
    "agentEmail": "jordanm@century21bcs.com",
    "thumbnailUrl": null,
    "price": 14645,
    "date": "2021-09-15",
    "startTime": "08:00:00",
    "endTime": "09:00:00"
  },
  "mlsNumber": "154564",
  "feedback": [
        {
            "question": "Is your client interested in this listing?",
            "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Please rate your overall experience at this showing.?",
          "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Your (and your client's) opinion of the price:?",
          "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Please rate this listing (5=Best; 1=Worst):",
          "answer": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "COMMENTS/RECOMMENDATIONS:",
          "answer": "dasdsadsadd"
        }
      ]
  },
  {
    "appointmentId": "324324244",
    "appointmentInfo": {
      "fullAddress": "18715 Keystone Oak Street, Manila",
      "listingId": 41156570,
      "listingAgent": "Jordan Delaney Miller",
      "office": "Keller Williams Woodlands",
      "agentEmail": "jordanm@century21bcs.com",
      "thumbnailUrl": null,
      "price": 14645,
      "date": "2021-09-15",
      "startTime": "08:00:00",
      "endTime": "09:00:00"
    },
    "mlsNumber": "154564",
    "feedback": [
        {
            "question": "Is your client interested in this listing?",
            "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Please rate your overall experience at this showing.?",
          "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Your (and your client's) opinion of the price:?",
          "answer": "YES"
        },
        {
          "question": "Please rate this listing (5=Best; 1=Worst):",
          "answer": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "COMMENTS/RECOMMENDATIONS:",
          "answer": "dasdsadsadd"
        }
      ]
  }
]
